ANTHONY J. SCHIESZ

Brooklyn, New York 407.325.3672 anthony.schiesz@gmail.com anthonyschiesz.github.io https://github.com/AnthonySchiesz linkedin.com/in/anthony-schiesz

Experienced medical administrative specialist with 5+ years of experience looking to leverage extensive background in healthcare relations into a career as a Software Engineer. Experience in the healthcare industry developed the understanding of client needs to develop better solutions.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, Javascript, HTML5, CSS

Frameworks/Libraries: ¡Query, Django, Jinja, Knockout.js (MVVM), AJAX, Bootstrap

PROJECTS

History Map - <u>anthonyschiesz.github.io/historymap</u>

- Responsive, single-page web application built with Knockout.js and hosted on GitHub pages.
- Designed and built interactive history map displaying marked and unmarked historical locations in the greater New York area with data parsed from Wikipedia.

Theory Blog - anthonyschiesz.github.io/multi-user-blog

- Responsive multi-user blog with content filtering powered by AJAX.
- Created with the Python framework to enable user authentication for posting and comments.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Fusion Physical Therapy - *Medical Administrative Specialist* New York, NY | 03.2016 - Present

- Coordinate with local medical facilities and build mutual partnerships for patient referrals.
- Develop and implement new policies and procedures to utilize EMR (Electronic Medical Record) software for a more effective patient turnaround.

Sand Lake Dermatology Center - Insurance Lead

Orlando, FL | 12.2014 - 03.2016

- Lead a team of 3 in completing department goals for insurance verification.
- Maintained database and scheduled for 5 physicians and 115 daily patients.

Southwest Orlando Family Medicine - Insurance Specialist Orlando, FL | 11.2012 - 12.2014

- Managed health data on multiple EMRs for 8 physicians and 130 daily patients.
- Validated insurance policies and benefits through online insurance portals.

EDUCATION & HONORS

Udacity | Full-Stack Web Developer Nanodegree Valencia College | Associates in Science Boy Scouts of America | Eagle Scout

12.2016 - Present 08.2010 - 2012 08.2008 - Present